<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[b-r.io RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Miro Tammi is a Software Engineer based out of Finland.]]></description><link>http://mtemedia.org</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 10:50:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Gaining productivity]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, how to actually gain productivity? I wanted to write in a list-like manner for you to pin the most beneficial ways to you. Set goals and…]]></description><link>http://mtemedia.org/gainprod/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://mtemedia.org/gainprod/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 22:09:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;So, how to actually gain productivity?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;I wanted to write in a list-like manner for you to pin the most beneficial ways to you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Set goals and prioritize your tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start your day by setting clear goals and prioritizing your to-do list. This will help you stay focused and motivated throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Eliminate distractions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify and eliminate distractions that can hinder your productivity, such as social media, email notifications, and messaging apps. You can use apps like Freedom or Focus@Will to help you stay focused.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Take breaks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking short breaks can actually help improve productivity. Try the Pomodoro Technique - working for 25 minutes, then taking a 5-minute break. Repeat the cycle 4 times, then take a longer break.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Exercise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Incorporate exercise into your daily routine. Exercise can help improve your mood, energy levels, and overall productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Eat a healthy diet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A healthy diet can help improve energy levels and concentration. Eating healthy foods like fruits, vegetables, proteins, and complex carbohydrates can help improve productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Use productivity tools&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are several productivity tools available that can help you stay on track and manage your time effectively. Tools like Trello, Todoist, and Google Calendar can help you stay organized and focused.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Make time for self-care&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking care of yourself is necessary for productivity. Make sure to get enough sleep, rest when needed, and participate in hobbies and activities that rejuvenate and energize you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By following these tips, you can improve your productivity and achieve your goals with less stress and more satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feel free to contact me in case you have anything in your mind.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why productivity]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, why productivity? As an introductory blog I suppose I should tell something about myself?... Currently studying computer science at uni…]]></description><link>http://mtemedia.org/whyprod/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://mtemedia.org/whyprod/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 22:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;So, why productivity?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;As an introductory blog I suppose I should tell something about myself?…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently studying computer science at uni, still young with much to learn. Not sure what will if anything come out of this blog, who knows?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So why a blog? I know I have a lot give and I have been dealing with productivity the last atleast 5-6 years. Wanting to be the best and not just wishing for things to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I haven’t done much creative in my life, so writing will be a way to sort of work on that area. My native language is not english, so apologies in before hand for the typos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This whole ride will teach me plenty and hoping to teach others how to develop, maintain and share productivity. Productivity will take us places but the risk of burning out or losing on the important moments is issue that can be dealt with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What’s next&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will probably think about themes and different topics to write here. This will not only focus on productivity but I’m trying to find a direction for this page and projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So will see what the future holds…&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>