<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[b-r.io RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Miro Tammi is a Software Engineer based out of Houston, TX.]]></description><link>https://b-r.io</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 11:51:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Why productivity]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, why productivity? As an introductory blog I suppose I should tell something about myself?... Currently studying computer science at uni…]]></description><link>https://b-r.io/whyprod/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://b-r.io/whyprod/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 22:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;So, why productivity?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;As an introductory blog I suppose I should tell something about myself?…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently studying computer science at uni, still young with much to learn. Not sure what will if anything come out of this blog, who knows?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So why a blog? I know I have a lot give and I have been dealing with productivity the last atleast 5-6 years. Wanting to be the best and not just wishing for things to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I haven’t done much creative in my life, so writing will be a way to sort of work on that area. My native language is not english, so apologies in before hand for the typos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This whole ride will teach me plenty and hoping to teach others how to develop, maintain and share productivity. Productivity will take us places but the risk of burning out or losing on the important moments is issue that can be dealt with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What’s next&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will probably think about themes and different topics to write here. This will not only focus on productivity but I’m trying to find a direction for this page and projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So will see what the future holds…&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>