<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[b-r.io RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Miro Tammi is a Software Engineer based out of Finland.]]></description><link>http://mtemedia.org</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:54:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[My best tools for productivity]]></title><description><![CDATA[What are the best tools? There are multiple tools to improve and help with your productivity. I will be going through the most common ones…]]></description><link>http://mtemedia.org/prodtools/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://mtemedia.org/prodtools/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 22:14:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;What are the best tools?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are multiple tools to improve and help with your productivity. I will be going through the most common ones and the ones that are the easiest to implement in your daily life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have realized that all the tools I use need to be easy access and work well. Having tried out multiple different tools these are some of my favourite. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Todoist or a ToDo app&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Never worry about forgetting those small tasks anymore. Take a simple ToDo -app into your daily life and ease your brainload. Having to remember those small tasks can be overwhelming and usually you always forget that one task.
Benefits of an app like Todoist is that you can have it on multiple devices. Whenever I remember something I need to get done I just instantly mark it on Todoist. Therefore I’m always on top of my tasks and not the other way around
Set yourself daily goals like completing 4 tasks for example and enjoy the satisfaction of completing those. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Calendar&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Write done your schedule now if you haven’t already. Mark important meetings in the calendar and try to keep it completely empty after 6 pm. It’s very important to make sure you rest efficiently.
Having all of your goings on your calendar rests your brain more, since you don’t have to worry about remember all the times and places. In productivity it’s important to make sure to take load off your brain and aim the energy at actually doing the tasks and activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Dream map / ToDo spreadsheet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have developed a personalized spreadsheet for a whole year and put my goals in there and important ToDos. I use this more as a long goal tool. Make the goals early in the year and you will always know what you are going towards. Let it be a new certificate or completing a major school assingment for example.
If you have any questions about making you a personal productivity plan feel free to contact me!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Notes on the phone on the go&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Need to make a quick shopping list, or want to write a message ready on the go. Make sure to utilize all the tools around you. I mostly use this for a bit longer ToDos or shopping lists for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Pen and paper&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The old-fashioned way or still a stable way? This is really good for some since you physically see the note and that works your brain in a different way.
You can never go wrong with post-it notes. These are also a really good way to teach a friend about something and the saying goes: when you teach you learn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everybody is completely different and some of these might not work but for some these are lifesaving. Give it a try and let me know how you feel about these and if there is some you think are really good.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gaining productivity]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, how to actually gain productivity? I wanted to write in a list-like manner for you to pin the most beneficial ways to you. Set goals and…]]></description><link>http://mtemedia.org/gainprod/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://mtemedia.org/gainprod/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 22:09:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;So, how to actually gain productivity?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;I wanted to write in a list-like manner for you to pin the most beneficial ways to you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Set goals and prioritize your tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start your day by setting clear goals and prioritizing your to-do list. This will help you stay focused and motivated throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Eliminate distractions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify and eliminate distractions that can hinder your productivity, such as social media, email notifications, and messaging apps. You can use apps like Freedom or Focus@Will to help you stay focused.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Take breaks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking short breaks can actually help improve productivity. Try the Pomodoro Technique - working for 25 minutes, then taking a 5-minute break. Repeat the cycle 4 times, then take a longer break.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Exercise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Incorporate exercise into your daily routine. Exercise can help improve your mood, energy levels, and overall productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Eat a healthy diet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A healthy diet can help improve energy levels and concentration. Eating healthy foods like fruits, vegetables, proteins, and complex carbohydrates can help improve productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Use productivity tools&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are several productivity tools available that can help you stay on track and manage your time effectively. Tools like Trello, Todoist, and Google Calendar can help you stay organized and focused.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Make time for self-care&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking care of yourself is necessary for productivity. Make sure to get enough sleep, rest when needed, and participate in hobbies and activities that rejuvenate and energize you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By following these tips, you can improve your productivity and achieve your goals with less stress and more satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feel free to contact me in case you have anything in your mind.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why productivity]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, why productivity? As an introductory blog I suppose I should tell something about myself?... Currently studying computer science at uni…]]></description><link>http://mtemedia.org/whyprod/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://mtemedia.org/whyprod/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 22:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;So, why productivity?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;As an introductory blog I suppose I should tell something about myself?…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently studying computer science at uni, still young with much to learn. Not sure what will if anything come out of this blog, who knows?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So why a blog? I know I have a lot give and I have been dealing with productivity the last atleast 5-6 years. Wanting to be the best and not just wishing for things to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I haven’t done much creative in my life, so writing will be a way to sort of work on that area. My native language is not english, so apologies in before hand for the typos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This whole ride will teach me plenty and hoping to teach others how to develop, maintain and share productivity. Productivity will take us places but the risk of burning out or losing on the important moments is issue that can be dealt with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What’s next&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will probably think about themes and different topics to write here. This will not only focus on productivity but I’m trying to find a direction for this page and projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So will see what the future holds…&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>